<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' ?>
<editorial>
	<header>
	</header>
	<body>
		<title_3>Welcome to rc-seller.com, the first inplementacion of the rc-seller project</title_3>
		<subheading_3>we are asociated with the developement of the rc-network platform </subheading_3>
		<paragraph_1>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=\&quot;float: right; margin: 1em; width: 180px; height: 153px;\&quot; src=\&quot;logo.jpg\&quot; alt=\&quot;\&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are a social network focused on the &lt;em&gt;research chemical scene&lt;/em&gt;. our plateform is modeled and developed upon two opensource projects. As a Plateform we provide an anoniomus exclusive and private chain of trusted relations that allow cooperative, distributed markerplace, based on  and collaborative set of tools, catalogues of alias and roles to provide services that integrates the requierements to the participation in an distributed and autogestioned sotial comunity as is &lt;strong&gt;rc-seller.es&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;&lt;a href=\&quot;http://sourceforge.net/donate/index.php?group_id=371664\&quot;&gt;Donate rc-network!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As services providers that have access to critic and sensitive information, we need the resources to support a reliable hosting infrastructure. The platform need also legal experts to help to fill the information leak in certain aspects: Study of the financial treatment of operations that will be anonymous and catalog of on legal requirements considering the context international trade. Analise and catalog of information concerning laws on production, possession and transport of different items. And this must also be in a comparative manner considering different body regions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The platform aims to be the rigth  place to analize the problems, discurs the altetrnative solutions too the differets problematics,and  design , develop and audit  the tools and services needed, Finalement we act as a task force who articipate and influence in the responsibles autorities  articulating alternatives and proposing them cost nalysys, adecuate  normatives, requirements and rules, propose legal mechanisms and finaly provde the tools and solutions that our platform needed to the  sucessful develop of our mision&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a platform, we want to provide invitations to others serlf managed groups and actorsable to fill the roles that expand and produce the normlized requierements needed to participate on the network As producers we want to be able to prvide sources of viable and verifiable hitorical information needed for the correct functionnement of the agents and ornaizations that are responsable as harm reduction agens. Another important problem we want to solve is the histyorical lack of estructured acces of this inforemation  that, evidently is also neded by the healt autorities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finaly, it\'s also our role to providing and grant the accessibility to other historical aspects that are also uselful to record and track the long term efects of substances over the popularton. The plateform is also responsible to etablish recolect and grant the validity of the indicators needed for for the auditory of tasks and roles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally,&lt;strong&gt;rc-shop.es&lt;/strong&gt;, as a project of incubation, exposes the issues and dificulties than then can be the discursed in the main place for debating policies, definin roles and fianlly desiging de plataform: the &lt;a href=\&quot;http:///rc-seller.sourceforge.net\&quot;&gt; project on sourceforge. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=\&quot;http:///rc-seller.sourceforge.net\&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=\&quot;http://sourceforge.net/donate/index.php?group_id=371664\&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=\&quot;http://images.sourceforge.net/images/project-support.jpg\&quot; border=\&quot;0\&quot; alt=\&quot;Support This Project\&quot; width=\&quot;88\&quot; height=\&quot;32\&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</paragraph_1>
		<paragraph_3>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;rc-seller.com&lt;/strong&gt;, is an incubation of the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=\&quot;http://rc-seller.sourceforge.net\&quot;&gt; rc-seller project on sourceforge. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. As a prototype, we expose the issues and dificulties that then can be the discursed in the main place for debating policies, defining roles and requierements: &lt;a href=\&quot;http://sourceforge.net/donate/index.php?group_id=371664\&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;rc-network platform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The result of this collaboration is fianlly defining an API that has to be implemented by sellers and resellers that want to operate in the plateform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=\&quot;text-align:center\&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=\&quot;https://sourceforge.net/project/project_donations.php?group_id=371664\&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=\&quot;http://images.sourceforge.net/images/project-support.jpg\&quot; border=\&quot;0\&quot; alt=\&quot;Support rc-network Project\&quot; width=\&quot;88\&quot; height=\&quot;32\&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=\&quot;text-align:center\&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=\&quot;https://sourceforge.net/donate/index.php?group_id=370391\&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=\&quot;http://images.sourceforge.net/images/project-support.jpg\&quot; border=\&quot;0\&quot; alt=\&quot;Support rc-seller Project\&quot; width=\&quot;88\&quot; height=\&quot;32\&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</paragraph_3>
		<home_logo_link>http://rcseller.es</home_logo_link>
	</body>
</editorial>
